JULIEN AFONSO

WEB DEVELOPER



1 090-8880-4393

ju.afonso61@gmail.com

Kyoto, Japan

in linkedin.com/in/julienafonso/

https://github.com/JulianTheOne

https://julienafonso.me/

PROFILE

Curious by nature, I moved to Japan 9 years ago and I have experience in Supply Chain, Sales, and E-commerce. I have transitioned into tech after learning coding. I am passionate about web development and I am eager to work in a collaborative, multi-cultural team environment.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- SQL
- Git/GitHub
- Heroku
- Ruby
- Ruby on Rails

EXPERIENCE

SALES ASSISTANT

Mercedes-Benz Kyoto Chuo (Jan 2022 - Dec 2022)

- 車検継続/希望ナンバー/名義変更/登録/車庫証明
- 新車納車準備 / 中古車納車準備 / ETCセットアップ

CO-FOUNDER

The Omamori Shop (Jul 2020 - Dec 2022)

- Shopify E-commerce connected to Ship&co API to optimize worldwide shipping
- Ads manager for multi-platform campaigns
- Collaboration with famous Japanese car Shop & US based influencers

EDUCATION

LE WAGON TOKYO|BATCH #1105

Web Development course (2023)

10-week intensive Full stack Developer bootcamp.

AFT-IFTIM CERELOG

Bachelor degree (2009)

Logistics, Materials and Supply Chain Management.

TRAVEL SALES CONSULTANT

Au fil du Japon - Freelance (Jul 2017 - Apr 2020) Autrement le Japon - (Sep 2014 - Oct 2016)

- Travel agent specialized on tailor made trip for B2B and B2C
- Accompanying travelers (Kyoto Osaka KIX)

WAREHOUSE MANAGER

BASF Coatings Services S.A. (Apr 2010 - Mar 2014)

 Logistics, inventory management with audit (KPMG), cost control, tester for ERP updates before national release (SAP)